nessus-v6-api-sample
====================
Nessus v6 REST API sample for C#/.NET4.5
login/logout, launch, export, and download scan.


requirement
====================
- Json.NET (install with NuGet)
- Add Reference for System.Net.Http


license
====================
Copyright © 2016 takutoy <takutoy@live.jp>
This work is free. You can redistribute it and/or modify it under the
terms of the Do What The Fuck You Want To Public License, Version 2,
as published by Sam Hocevar. See http://www.wtfpl.net/ for more details.

            DO WHAT THE FUCK YOU WANT TO PUBLIC LICENSE
   TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR COPYING, DISTRIBUTION AND MODIFICATION

  0. You just DO WHAT THE FUCK YOU WANT TO.
